<resources>
    <string name="app_name">About Me</string>
    <string name="name">Nilton Pontes</string>
    <string name="yellow_star">Yellow Star</string>
    <string name="bio">About Me  Hello! I\'m Nilton Pontes, a passionate Kotlin programmer with a love for crafting elegant and efficient software solutions. Let me take a moment to tell you a bit about myself.  I embarked on my programming journey with a deep curiosity for technology and its limitless possibilities. As I delved into the world of software development, I discovered the beauty of Kotlin, a language that perfectly blends power, expressiveness, and safety.  With several years of experience in Kotlin, I have honed my skills and become proficient in leveraging its features to create robust and scalable applications. Whether it\'s developing Android apps, building backend services, or working on cross-platform solutions, Kotlin has always been my go-to language due to its conciseness and interoperability.  Throughout my career, I have actively participated in various software development projects, collaborating with talented teams to deliver high-quality solutions. I am well-versed in modern software development practices, including agile methodologies and test-driven development, which enables me to write clean and maintainable code.  I am particularly fascinated by the versatility of Kotlin and its ability to seamlessly integrate with existing Java codebases. I enjoy utilizing Kotlin\'s powerful features, such as coroutines and functional programming constructs, to create efficient and responsive applications. Embracing best practices, I always strive to follow clean architecture principles and design patterns that ensure the scalability and extensibility of my projects.  Aside from technical skills, I believe in effective communication and teamwork. I enjoy collaborating with diverse professionals, exchanging ideas, and learning from their expertise. I thrive in an environment where creativity and innovation are encouraged, and where I can contribute my skills to build remarkable software solutions.  When I\'m not coding, you can find me exploring the latest trends and advancements in the tech world, attending programming meetups, or experimenting with new libraries and frameworks. I believe in continuous learning and growth, and I\'m always excited to expand my knowledge and stay up-to-date with the latest industry developments.  If you\'re looking for a dedicated Kotlin programmer who is passionate about creating clean and efficient code, I would love to discuss how I can contribute to your projects. Feel free to reach out, and let\'s embark on an exciting journey of crafting exceptional software together!  Thank you for taking the time to learn a bit about me. I look forward to connecting with you soon!</string>
    <string name="nickname">What is your nickname?</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
</resources>